Yes, review online, so it says edit the online, then click an option below, each heading
corresponds to a paragraph, right?
And yes, the best path for beginners to learn French, so it says reasons to learn French
essential beginner resources and immersive learning strategies, right?
And these are the main points that are going to be mentioned in each paragraph.
So it can edit these freely, right?
So I can come here and say, "Wily spoken globally," I can remove this item and add
my own, right?
So I can say, "Macron speaks it."
I can replace that item with this one and it will generate the text based on this, right?
So this is the outline that we have.
This is called outline, as you see.
One credit is removed out of our daily credits, so we have nine out of ten.